<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Jetpack Compose In 30 days</string>
    <string name="day1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="day11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="day12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="day13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="day14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="day15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="day16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="day17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="day18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="day19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="day20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="day21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="day22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="day23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="day24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="day25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="day26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="day27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="day28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="day29">Day 29</string>
    <string name="day30">Day 30</string>

    <string name="task1">Getting Started with Jetpack Compose</string>
    <string name="task2"> Understanding Composables</string>
    <string name="task3">Creating Custom Composables</string>
    <string name="task4">Adding Interactivity</string>
    <string name="task5">Working with Lists</string>
    <string name="task6">Navigation</string>
    <string name="task7">Theming</string>
    <string name="task8">Layouts</string>
    <string name="task9">Animations</string>
    <string name="task10">Material Design</string>
    <string name="task11">Modifiers</string>
    <string name="task12">Forms</string>
    <string name="task13"> Images and Icons</string>
    <string name="task14">Draw</string>
    <string name="task15">Working with Data</string>
    <string name="task16">Text and Typography</string>
    <string name="task17">Accessibility</string>
    <string name="task18">Debugging</string>
    <string name="task19">Testing</string>
    <string name="task20">Integration with View System</string>
    <string name="task21">Debugging with Stetho</string>
    <string name="task22">Navigation</string>
    <string name="task23">Animations</string>
    <string name="task24">Custom Layouts</string>
    <string name="task25">Material Design</string>
    <string name="task26">Theming</string>
    <string name="task27">Accessibility with TalkBack</string>
    <string name="task28">Internationalization and Localization</string>
    <string name="task29">Publishing to Google Play</string>
    <string name="task30"> Beyond the Basics</string>

    <string name="desc1">Explore the basics of Jetpack Compose by setting up a new project, understanding the project structure, and creating a simple user interface. Here\'s an example of how to create a simple layout using the Composable function.</string>
    <string name="desc2">Learn how to create reusable Composable functions and how to use them to create more complex layouts. By understanding Composables, you can create a flexible and scalable user interface.</string>
    <string name="desc3">Explore the different types of custom Composable functions and how to create them. By creating custom Composables, you can create your own reusable building blocks that can be used across your entire project.</string>
    <string name="desc4">Learn how to add user interactivity to your Jetpack Compose UI by using state and events. By adding interactivity, you can create a more dynamic and engaging user experience.</string>
    <string name="desc5">Explore the different ways to create lists in Jetpack Compose and how to customize them. By working with lists, you can create a more organized and easy-to-use user interface.</string>
    <string name="desc6">Learn how to create a navigation system in Jetpack Compose, including setting up a navigation graph, navigating between screens, and passing data between screens.</string>
    <string name="desc7">Explore the different ways to apply themes to your Jetpack Compose UI and how to customize them. By using themes, you can create a consistent and visually appealing user interface.</string>
    <string name="desc8">Learn how to use different types of layouts in Jetpack Compose, including ConstraintLayout and Box. By understanding layouts, you can create a more organized and visually appealing user interface.</string>
    <string name="desc9">Explore how to create animations in Jetpack Compose, including animating properties, creating animations using keyframes, and using the Transition API.</string>
    <string name="desc10">Learn how to use Material Design in Jetpack Compose, including using the Material Design components and applying Material Design styles and themes.</string>
    <string name="desc11">Understand how to use modifiers in Jetpack Compose, including how to apply padding, alignment, and size to your UI elements.</string>
    <string name="desc12">Learn how to create forms in Jetpack Compose, including using text fields, checkboxes, radio buttons, and other form elements.</string>
    <string name="desc13">Explore how to add images and icons to your Jetpack Compose UI, including using the Image composable and the Icon composable.</string>
    <string name="desc14">Understand how to use the Draw composable in Jetpack Compose, including how to draw shapes, paths, and text on the canvas.</string>
    <string name="desc15">Learn how to work with data in Jetpack Compose, including using LiveData and ViewModel to observe and update data in your UI.</string>
    <string name="desc16">Explore how to use different text styles and typography in Jetpack Compose, including using the Text composable and the Typography library.</string>
    <string name="desc17">Understand how to create an accessible user interface in Jetpack Compose, including using the accessibility tools provided by Android.</string>
    <string name="desc18">Learn how to debug your Jetpack Compose UI using Android Studio, including using the Layout Inspector and the Compose Preview.</string>
    <string name="desc19">Explore how to write tests for your Jetpack Compose UI using the AndroidX Test Library, including writing unit tests and UI tests.</string>
    <string name="desc20">Understand how to integrate Jetpack Compose with the existing View System, including using the AndroidView composable and the Interoperability library.</string>
    <string name="desc21">Learn how to use Stetho, a debugging tool for Android apps, to debug your Jetpack Compose UI.</string>
    <string name="desc22">Understand how to use the Navigation component in Jetpack Compose, including how to define destinations and navigate between them.</string>
    <string name="desc23">Learn how to add animations to your Jetpack Compose UI, including using the Animatable and AnimatedVisibility composables.</string>
    <string name="desc24">Explore how to create custom layouts in Jetpack Compose, including using the ConstraintLayout and the Box composable.</string>
    <string name="desc25">Understand how to use Material Design in Jetpack Compose, including using the Material Theme and the Material Design components.</string>
    <string name="desc26">Learn how to create and apply custom themes in Jetpack Compose, including using the Theme composable and the attributes provided by Android. </string>
    <string name="desc27">Understand how to create an accessible user interface in Jetpack Compose, including using TalkBack, the accessibility tool provided by Android.</string>
    <string name="desc28">Explore how to internationalize and localize your Jetpack Compose UI, including using the string resources provided by Android.</string>
    <string name="desc29">Learn how to publish your Jetpack Compose app to Google Play, including creating a release build and uploading it to the Google Play Console.</string>
    <string name="desc30">Explore more advanced features of Jetpack Compose, including using animation libraries, custom layouts, and more.</string>

</resources>